Lend me your power, Ashuramaru.
Is this what they call "demon possession"?
No, there's more to it than that.
While in this state, you need to cut yourself, and let your weapon drink your blood.
Drink my blood?
That's kinda vampire-ish.
Well, demons and vampires have a lot in common.
Should I explain?
Nah, that's fine.
Let's do this, Yuu.
Hold it.
It'll be a real problem for us if both of you mess up at the same time.
If you fail,
there's a risk your demons may go out of control.
That's why we came all the way outside the walls.
Out of control...
What is it?
Nothing.
Guys!
What is it?
There are horsemen coming.
Three...
Four...
Five of them.
What terrible timing...
No point complaining, let's just get rid of them.
Strike the enemy, Gekkouin!
We'll protect everyone!
I did it, guys!
Hey, you...
Did you just bring out your demon?
Hey, Shinoa, what's going on here!?
Did you already train this guy?
Oh, no.
Yoichi-san is just naturally talented in controlling his demon weapon.
He learned to manifest his demon by himself.
Seriously?
Well, I often chat with my demon at night,
and I guess at some point I started being able to manifest it.
Have some of my blood, Ashuramaru!
Wait, Yuu!
Weapons out!
Yuu-kun!?
What happened?
Well, at the very least he didn't lose control right away,
but it'll be a while before he makes contact with his demon.
Meanwhile, we'll be looking over him.
After all, that's what friends are for.
zutto yume miteita
I was always dreaming
kowaresou na kibou toki wo koe
Crumbling hopes crossed over time
kousa shita sorezore no yasashisa
Mixing together with different types of kindness
futo miageru sora ni kimi no egao egaku
I look up at the sky and imagine your smile
ano hi kara bokutachi wa chigau sekai wo mita
Ever since that day we've seen the world differently
omoi ga afureru
My feelings overflow
shinjiau koto wa tayasui koto da to
To place your trust in someone isn't hard
sono kioku wa shitteru
So those memories tell me
hikari to yami ni kakusareta kono michi wo susumu beku
To continue along this road hidden in the light and shadow
futatsu no omoi ga kirameku
These two feelings sparkle
kimi wo mamoritai
I want to protect you
kokoro ni kanjiru kizuna wo dakishimete
Embrace the bonds you have tied
tachiagaru toki wa ima
The time to rise up is now
kanashimi kirisaite
Cut aside the sadness
two souls go toward the truth
sono egao wo sagashite
Searching for that smile
kono omoi ga bokura wo tsuyoku shinjitsu he to michibiku
These feelings guide us toward the truth
Tangled Bonds
Friends, huh.
Something on your mind?
Kimizuki-kun?
Earlier,
Yoichi and I were interrogated by those Hiiragis.
They wanted to know what exactly happened during that battle.
And what did you tell them?
That we didn't know anything about it.
Just like you told us to.
Good.
Is it really right to keep it secret from Yuu, though?
If this "friend" stuff is just an excuse to try and use Yuu...
What would you do?
Nothing.
I'm here for my sister's sake.
Even if that means having to endure this disgusting "friends" charade.
Hey, Kimizuki! Watch your mouth!
Shinoa is protecting Yuu from—
It's okay, Micchan.
Do you feel the same way, Yoichi-san?
Well, I...
I still believe that you're keeping this from Yuu-kun for his own good,
but...
You want a proper explanation?
Yeah.
We're...
friends, right?
We are.
Or at least, I'd like us to be.
So...
after this trial, I'll tell you everything.
Not just about Yuu-san, but about all of us.
Guys, keep him down!
Yuu-kun!
It's begun...
Yes, he's come into contact with his demon.
What did I do to deserve a child like this?
We have to kill the Seraph of the End.
You're a devil, Yuu.
The child of a devil.
D-Dad?
Come here, Yuu.
We'll go to a better place,
Yuu.
You should've died here.
Everyone died because you ran.
Surrender yourself, Yuu.
It'll take more than this to make me lose control, Ashuramaru.
There's something I need to do.
I made a promise with him.
He needs me.
Yuu-chan,
let's protect our family together.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah.
It's because you're counting on me
that I'll be able to save you.
Oh?
I thought I had you.
I've already got you figured out.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You're just some little devil, abandoned by your parents.
As long as Mika needs me...
As long as Guren and Shinoa need me...
I don't care what I am.
Oh? Looks like you've grown a bit since last time.
However...
That calm attitude really pisses me off.
What are you going to do about it?
I'll kill you.
What do you think you're doing!?
I don't want to hurt you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I need you, Ashuramaru.
Let's save Mika together.
And why should I do that?
Because I'll be your friend.
It's hard being alone.
Even harder if nobody needs you.
I know that well.
And that's why you'll be my friend?
Yeah!
Yuu!
Huh?
Did I cause any trouble?
You're back! You're back for real!
Man, you were thrashing around really hard.
I promise I didn't mean to.
So, did you win?
Yeah.
Then there's nothing to worry about.
But to be honest, I'm pretty tired after that.
Let's do Kimizuki's trial next week.
Screw that! We're doing it now!
Aw, do we really have to?
You too!?
Good job.
So, are you okay?
Your demon didn't hurt you?
I'm fine.
Thanks to you guys,
I know I'm not alone.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
Put simply,
humans are a bunch of defective animals and entirely incapable of controlling their greed,
which led to this taboo research.
Please have a look at this,
I'm sure you'll understand what I mean.
Hey, what the hell was that?
If they figure out how to control that...
Indeed!
The humans have finally managed to turn the Seraph of the End into a weapon!
This is a grave issue!
B-But didn't Krul-sama put a stop to that research by destroying the Hyakuya sect?
That's right.
I did stop it eight years ago.
I personally killed all of the children
carrying the Seraph of the End factor.
Oh, you killed all the experimental subjects?
That's what I just said—
Then please explain...
how they've been able to continue their research.
Apart from the Hyakuya sect,
there shouldn't have been any other
organizations researching this subject.
Should it be revealed that you failed to control this situation Krul,
the consequences would be—
Silence, Lest Karr.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?
What if I am?
If it's too much for you,
I'd be happy to take over the Japanese throne for you.
This is none of your business, brat.
Oh please, 200 years isn't such a big difference.
Besides, I think we both know I'm stronger—
Now, now,
you two.
Regardless, Krul-sama,
the humans did successfully create this weapon.
How are you planning to deal with it?
Our overall strategy will remain the same.
We'll deploy our main forces, and destroy the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
I'm looking forward to the results.
By the way, Ferid Bathory...
Who is that child behind you?
You bastard, what the hell are you up to!?
Why did you bring Mikaela?
And that footage...
Are you trying to set me up!?
My, how scary.
But you're not going to kill me.
Because if you do, all my incriminating intel might just end up in the Progenitor Council's hands.
Besides, I'd be in trouble too if it got out that I let Yuu-chan escape.
Oh, wait a second. Doesn't that make us partners in crime?
How exciting.
Take my hand, Krul Tepes.
Just kidding!
Let's keep working together, shall we?
Kru—
Kimizuki-kun,
hang in there!
Hey, Shinoa, was it like this with me too?
No, this might be even worse.
There's a chance that his demon will take over.
Then what are we supposed to do?
Yuu-san!
Prepare for the worst!
Die!
Such desperation!
Obey me, Kiseki-Ou!
I don't obey weaklings.
Your body is as good as mine.
Just give in.
Big brother...
Don't worry.
How is Mirai-chan doing?
Not good. It's advancing fast.
Listen, our food supply is running low.
It won't even last another three days.
Are we leaving?
Yeah, tomorrow morning.
Wait,
we need time to prepare for moving Mirai.
Forget Mirai.
She'll only hinder us.
What did you say?
Calm down!
Look, Kimizuki.
We've got a responsibility.
We need to be able to protect the other kids while we move tomorrow.
This world isn't nice enough to let us bring the sick with us.
You do it.
This is better for her.
This is crazy, how could I—
Mirai-chan asked for this!
She said she didn't want to be a burden on you anymore.
She would have done it herself, if she could move.
If you can't do it,
we will.
Hey!
Wait, Kimizuki!
Open up, Kimizuki!
Shit.
This way! We'll get in through the balcony!
Big brother?
Crap.
Hey, Big brother...
I don't want to slow you down.
Be quiet, Mirai.
Please,
kill me.
I'm tired of watching you go through all this for me.
Shut up!
Just shut up already!
Please!
There it is!
You just thought you wanted to be free of me.
"I've had enough."
"Why am I the only one going through all this?"
"I'm still just a kid."
"If only I could just kill her..."
No...
"If I could just be free of this pain..."
No!
That's what you were thinking, weren't you?
I wasn't!
You were, Kimizuki Shihou.
Stop resisting, and set yourself free.
Big brother, thank you for finally letting me rest in peace.
I'm sorry, Mirai.
There's nothing to apologize for.
This is what I wished for.
There's something I'd like to tell you, before this ends.
Recently...
I got to know this pretty weird guy.
He's so annoying.
I hate him.
So this guy...
He keeps saying he'll risk his life to save someone he's not even related to.
What's up with that?
He's a total idiot, don't you think?
Sounds like it.
But you know,
there's no way I can let an idiot like that get ahead of me.
Because I have family to protect too, one that's related by blood.
I'd do anything to avoid killing you.
Even...
Big brother, don't—
It's over.
You got me.
Come, Kiseki-Ou.
Yuu-san!
Calm down, guys. I'm okay.
Kimizuki-kun!
Hey!
Then why did you attack me!?
I think it's about time we decided once and for all which one of us is the strongest.
You overcame your trial too, huh?
And now, like before, I'm once again stronger than you.
Oh really?
Then how about we get to it?
Hey, cut it out you—
That's what I like to hear.
Don't you think this'll be fun to watch?
Come, Ashuramaru.
Unfold, Ashura Kannon!
No turning back now, Kimizuki.
Count to nine and open the coffin,
Kiseki-Ou!
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Ah, hey! Don't run away!
Yeah right, that thing looks like it means business!
It's giving off some really bad vibes!
He may be an idiot but he's got good senses.
What was that!?
Well, his stupidity is what saved me this time.
Hm?
I'm saying I'm tired of your shit!
Hey now, sounds like you haven't had enough!
Let's settle this right now!
That's enough guys, get along!
Sure, come at me!
Shinoa, was that...
Yes.
They were about to unleash abilities they wouldn't normally be able to use.
And we can't forget Yoichi being able to manifest his demon without any training.
Where did Lieutenant Colonel Guren find these guys?
Hey, what the hell does this mean?
As you can see,
someone's wiped all data on their pasts.
By "someone", you mean...
It must have been Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
Is he really planning to fight the upper echelon?
If it was just that, I wouldn't be so worried, but...
What?
Human experimentation,
and this war against the vampires...
I have a feeling something horrible is about to happen.
reimei ni tsuki wa koroge ochite
The moon rolls away into the dawn
shitatakana kirameki ni kakusareru
hiding in the strong light
kanjou ni kanketsu suru omoi
Emotions circling back to closure
dare no kokoro mo tsunagenai
I can't connect anyone's hearts
yuuen no inori
A distant prayer
shinjiteita chitsujo ga uso naraba
If the peace that we believed in was a lie,
jibun no kokoro sura jyunshoku wo shite
I will even fool my heart
furuitateru honoo wo matou
and clothe myself in an inspiring flame
umidashite wa hakai suru hakoniwa
A garden creates, then destroys everything
tatoe nigiru tsurugi ga moroha demo
even if the sword you hold is double-edged
subete wo ushinau made aragai, torikustaa
Fight until you lose everything, trickster
Next time on Owari no Seraph:
The Imperial Demon Army's Ambition
The Imperial Demon Army's Ambition.