Go get Guren.
zutto yume miteita
I was always dreaming
kowaresou na kibou toki wo koe
Crumbling hopes crossed over time
kousa shita sorezore no yasashisa
Mixing together with different types of kindness
futo miageru sora ni kimi no egao egaku
I look up at the sky and imagine your smile
ano hi kara bokutachi wa chigau sekai wo mita
Ever since that day we've seen the world differently
omoi ga afureru
My feelings overflow
shinjiau koto wa tayasui koto da to
To place your trust in someone isn't hard
sono kioku wa shitteru
So those memories tell me
hikari to yami ni kakusareta kono michi wo susumu beku
To continue along this road hidden in the light and shadow
futatsu no omoi ga kirameku
These two feelings sparkle
kimi wo mamoritai
I want to protect you
kokoro ni kanjiru kizuna wo dakishimete
Embrace the bonds you have tied
tachiagaru toki wa ima
The time to rise up is now
kanashimi kirisaite
Cut aside the sadness
two souls go toward the truth
sono egao wo sagashite
Searching for that smile
kono omoi ga bokura wo tsuyoku shinjitsu he to michibiku
These feelings guide us toward the truth
The Imperial Demon Army's Ambitions
Damn, why won't it stay down?
You've gotta dry your hair before you sleep.
I know that!
Whatever, it's fine.
It's fine?
It will be eventually.
Huh?
Where is it?
Room three.
Do you really think they can make a decent breakfast?
It'll be fine.
It's two girls, after all.
Oh yeah, what are we supposed to be talking about, anyway?
Do you two know anything?
So Yoichi, what do you think we'll be having?
Maybe something really fancy.
You do know something.
Come on, tell me.
You'll hear about it from Shinoa.
Until then, just worry about that bed head.
What are they up to?
Oh, well.
Hey, are you guys okay!?
You're going to burn it!
How in the world did you manage to set the omelette on fire!?
I read that it turns out better when you add alcohol!
Is that...
Here.
Take it out to the table.
This is pretty amazing, man!
You can do pretty much anything, huh?
No, you guys are just useless.
I would've done just fine without Micchan.
It was supposed to taste better with alcohol.
Well that's okay, we'll just have to wait until next time.
Just make sure there's an extinguisher nearby.
So, what are we talking about?
Can't say I like being the only one left out of the loop.
There are two things we're going to discuss.
First of all,
we have to talk about Yuu-san being a test subject,
and how he went berserk during combat, nearly killing me in the process.
Secondly,
we need to think about whether Lieutenant Colonel Guren is on our side or not.
Whether or not Guren is on our side?
What do you mean?
There's a possibility that he's not just
manipulating you, but the rest of us as well.
He might be using us in his fight against the brass,
or maybe he has even bigger plans.
I haven't heard about this either.
In any case,
we have to decide whether we'll go along with whatever Lieutenant Colonel Guren's up to...
Or rather, how we as a group will face this world.
We want to hear you guys' thoughts and opinions on this.
You're saying there's a possibility of us turning on the lieutenant colonel?
That's one option.
Blood...
There's blood...
Blood!
This is pretty distasteful,
Hiiragi Kureto.
You sure took your time.
Another demon weapon experiment?
Indeed.
I was thinking there might be a more efficient way to turn vampires into demons.
Doesn't seem like it, though.
I guess low-level trash won't do.
You can kill them.
Don't tell me what to do.
Just hurry up and tell me why I'm here.
Did you really come alone?
Wasn't that what you ordered?
It never occurred to you that you might be murdered here?
Why should I worry about that?
Because you're too cheeky.
If that was all I was, I'd have been dead a long time ago.
You won't kill me as long as you can use me.
You're right.
I won't kill you as long as long as you're useful.
So let me ask you a few questions to determine how useful you still are.
Hyakuya Yuuichirou...
Saotome Yoichi...
Kimizuki Shihou...
Who are those three?
How did you manage to create three Black Demon candidates?
I got lucky.
How else would I be able to find such unusually talented—
Impossible.
Every single Black Demon prospect came from human experimentation.
And very few people survive those experiments.
Well, it's fine.
It's not like having more Black Demon wielders is a bad thing.
Next time you get results like that, be sure to let me in on it.
If I feel like it.
Was that all you wanted?
If so, I'm leaving.
Next question.
Why are you suddenly gathering up Black Demon wielders?
Are you planning a coup d'état?
If I was,
it would make sense for me to cut you down right here and now.
As if you could.
Want to find out?
That brings me back.
But there's no need for that.
You're doing a fine job.
But I know your weakness.
Love and friendship.
You know very well that you're better off ignoring those things.
But you can't.
And that's exactly why I can trust you, Guren.
Because you can't betray your friends.
You won't ever be a threat to me.
Is this the part where you bring out another hostage?
Who is it this time?
What do you want to squeeze out of me?
Don't put it like that.
Guren,
what do you see in our future?
There's no point in surviving in a world like this.
I'm sure there are people who think like that.
Did you call me out here to complain?
I just want to know what your vision is.
This world is devoid of hopes and dreams,
and yet you continue to bolster your military power.
For what purpose?
Because this is a world where more power is always needed.
Naturally.
But why bother if you have nothing to strive for?
Those who sacrifice others in vain...
are evil.
Evil, huh?
I'm going to restore the world, Guren.
The vampires destroyed all means of communicating outside the country,
but I suspect there are other human organizations left out there.
Probably.
So for now your goal is to restore
communications with the rest of the world?
No.
First, I'm going to get rid of all the vampires in this country.
Then,
I'll subjugate every other remaining human organization.
My goal is to place the entire world under the Imperial Demon Army's control.
That's a pretty childish goal.
And yet undeniably glorious.
In order to achieve that goal, the first step will be to slaughter every last vampire noble.
What are the odds of you pulling that off?
There are currently 25 nobles in Japan.
And we know where each and every one of them is.
If you push your luck too far...
...I'll have the rug pulled out from under me?
Remember that the intel itself could also be a trap.
I know that.
But we don't have time to hesitate.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Next month,
the vampires are planning to attack Tokyo with their main force.
We'll be annihilated if we lose the initiative.
But if we act now...
...we can get them first?
Guren, take your people and a hundred others from the Moon Demon Company.
Head over to Nagoya.
There are ten nobles there right now, setting up a base.
Kill them and capture the base.
We'll turn a lot of heads doing that.
That's the idea.
It'll draw the enemy's attention away from us for a while.
That'll give us time to prepare the main battle.
So I'm just a sacrificial pawn?
I wouldn't be asking you if I didn't recognize your strength.
This is your most important mission.
If I can trust you to do this,
you can leave the rest to me.
In short, you're not going to tell me the real plan.
Some "trust" that is.
Here are your orders.
Anyway, just shut up and do what I say.
Follow me,
and I'll show you a world where the vampires are our livestock.
You're not going to listen to him, are you Guren?
You're loyal only to me.
Because if you obey me, I'll grant your wish.
Shut up.
Watching a girl change clothes or something?
Sheesh, all you ever do is tease me.
Then what were you looking at?
Hey...
Did I really almost kill you?
Well, life is full of surprises.
Whatever happened,
I'm still here,
alive and well.
That's all that matters.
I should have been protecting you.
Oh, it looks like you've finally understood our squad formation!
That is correct!
You and Kimizuki-san are the vanguard,
the knights of the Shinoa squad.
Please protect me with your life.
Yuu-san?
Did Guren know I'd lose control?
Probably.
If you still haven't decided...
I was looking west.
Say,
are you coming along when we go to beat up the vampires?
What makes you ask that?
Well, you know,
if it happens again...
There's no need to worry.
Then I'll trust you.
It's true that traveling such a distance will be a bit of a pain,
but there's nothing to be done about that.
Thanks.
Well, let's head back.
The others will probably get mad if we keep them waiting much longer.
I'm sticking with Guren.
He said we're all family.
Mitsuba,
Yoichi,
Kimizuki,
Shinoa...
He said you're all my new family.
I think so too.
You're all important to me.
But
I can't just forget about Mika.
He's also an important part of my family.
I was abandoned by my parents so maybe I don't know what "family" really means,
but...
if you're betrayed by family,
does that really mean you should turn on them?
Guren said he'd help me get Mika back.
I'm going to believe him.
I know I'm being selfish, and I hate to drag you guys into it,
but I—
That's enough.
I think you and I have the same idea of family.
Right?
Yeah!
It looks like like we've come to a decision.
Family first.
In a world as bleak as this, it's certainly an unexpected thing to focus on.
But that's how the Shinoa squad is going to fight.
Well, after you fix your bed head.
Hey!
Oh? Mika, you're here.
You're just in time, I was preparing your—
Were you that thirsty?
My, you're hopeless.
I-I'm sorry, Krul.
Anyone would do the same in your place.
Um, could I have more bl—
...a larger supply this time?
I'll give you as much as you desire.
But
my blood won't always be enough to satisfy you.
Eventually that day will come.
Wait for me in the other room.
I'll call for you when I'm done.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Weren't
you supposed to have killed Yuu-chan and me?
Oh, now that's a surpise.
Are you worried about me?
Why did you take such a risk to save us?
What are you trying to do with us?
That's
not something you need to worry about.
Don't give me that!
If you're trying to use Yuu-chan...
And what if I am?
You're nothing more than my pet.
I can't just blindly follow you anymore.
Goodness, you're always so selfish.
But I'm not as cruel as the humans.
Because to be honest, I'm fond of you two.
I can't trust you.
You can and you will.
Fine.
I'll tell you why I let you live.
Why I need the Seraph of the End.
The war begins in a month.
This time, we're deploying our main force to kill every last human in this country.
It'll be a grand clash between vampires and humans.
As for you, Mika,
you will go and retrieve Yuu,
staying hidden from both humans and vampires.
This is a top secret mission.
If you fail, the entire world will be your enemy.
Understood.
I'll save Yuu-chan from both the humans and vampires.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Lieutenant Colonel, Yuu-san and Kimizuki-san have both finished their training,
and succeeded in manifesting their demons.
That so?
Yes.
You asked me before whether I'd fallen for Yuu-san.
I don't remember that.
So, have you?
I don't actually know.
But for the first time ever, someone told me they needed me.
I think I'd like to live up to that.
And with that, please excuse me.
Shinoa, I have sortie orders for you.
Tomorrow at 0600 hours,
report to the staging area.
We're going to kill the vampires in Nagoya.
You got the order too?
Apparently we're moving the main force to Nagoya, before deploying to Tokyo.
I heard.
Increase sensitivity on the left.
Roger.
Kureto-sama,
the preparations are complete.
Do it.
Increase the load.
More power.
B-But...
At this rate the subject might die.
Do it.
reimei ni tsuki wa koroge ochite
The moon rolls away into the dawn
shitatakana kirameki ni kakusareru
hiding in the strong light
kanjou ni kanketsu suru omoi
Emotions circling back to closure
dare no kokoro mo tsunagenai
I can't connect anyone's hearts
yuuen no inori
A distant prayer
shinjiteita chitsujo ga uso naraba
If the peace that we believed in was a lie,
jibun no kokoro sura jyunshoku wo shite
I will even fool my heart
furuitateru honoo wo matou
and clothe myself in an inspiring flame
umidashite wa hakai suru hakoniwa
A garden creates, then destroys everything
tatoe nigiru tsurugi ga moroha demo
even if the sword you hold is double-edged
subete wo ushinau made aragai, torikustaa
Fight until you lose everything, trickster
Next time on Owari no Seraph:
The Moon Demon's Command
The Moon Demon's Command.