zutto yume miteita
I was always dreaming
kowaresou na kibou toki wo koe
Crumbling hopes crossed over time
kousa shita sorezore no yasashisa
Mixing together with different types of kindness
futo miageru sora ni kimi no egao egaku
I look up at the sky and imagine your smile
ano hi kara bokutachi wa chigau sekai wo mita
Ever since that day we've seen the world differently
omoi ga afureru
My feelings overflow
shinjiau koto wa tayasui koto da to
To place your trust in someone isn't hard
sono kioku wa shitteru
So those memories tell me
hikari to yami ni kakusareta kono michi wo susumu beku
To continue along this road hidden in the light and shadow
futatsu no omoi ga kirameku
These two feelings sparkle
kimi wo mamoritai
I want to protect you
kokoro ni kanjiru kizuna wo dakishimete
Embrace the bonds you have tied
tachiagaru toki wa ima
The time to rise up is now
kanashimi kirisaite
Cut aside the sadness
two souls go toward the truth
sono egao wo sagashite
Searching for that smile
kono omoi ga bokura wo tsuyoku shinjitsu he to michibiku
These feelings guide us toward the truth
Sword of Justice
I'm so full!
Chess, you're not supposed to kill the hostages.
What? Seriously?
Hey, you heard her! You're not allowed to die!
Goodness.
S-Sorry about that, Crowley-sama!
Eh, who cares?
We've got more of them.
Well that's that, then!
Here, Horn, you have some too!
Show some restraint.
You call yourself a noble?
Jeez, how can you stand to be so stiff all the time?
What do you think, Crowley-sama?
I think you could learn a little from her.
Aw, come on!
Anyway, Crowley-sama,
what do you think about the situation?
To think the humans would come all the way to Nagoya...
Well...
Hey Chess,
come over here for a moment.
Okay...
Wh-What was that for?
I just wanted to see how strong the humans' weapons are, compared to our own gear.
Anything would be strong in your hands, Crowley-sama.
That's not the point.
Then what is?
Well, I think there might be something unnatural about how fast the humans are getting stronger.
Weapons coated in demon curses and
designed to exterminate vampires, huh?
See,
what if one of ours was actually leaking information like this to them?
You're suggesting there might be a traitor among us?
And not just anyone, but someone near the top.
As you can see, it's not healing.
So I want you two to be extra careful.
I'll treat you right away.
You can have some, if you want.
B-But, Crowley-sama...
I'll take it, then!
You just got some from that human.
It's my turn now.
That's not fair!
Not fair! Not fair! Not fair!
Is something the matter?
I can't help but wonder who's really pulling the strings behind this grand conflict.
Krul Tepes, maybe? Ferid Bathory?
Or...
Or?
Surely it couldn't be the humans.
So, how long are we supposed to be on standby here?
Until the other squads have arrived.
And when's that supposed to be?
At 14:20.
What time is it now?
14:13.
Where's Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose?
He's not here yet.
I see.
Standby until 14:20.
Ma'am.
Shinoa.
The other groups had three five-man teams, didn't they?
Yes.
The others probably died.
Aihara.
Did you accomplish your mission?
We wouldn't be here if we hadn't.
Your team came out unscathed?
I guess our leader's just that good.
Cut it out.
Wouldn't you say so, Squad Leader Hiiragi Shinoa?
What? You're putting this onto me?
Um, well...
I'm glad you came back alive.
We've got this covered, so take it easy for a bit.
Is that the newbie?
Yeah.
I think his name was...
You seriously forgot?
After all your talk about remembering the name of the enemy!
Just kidding.
This is Hyakuya Yuuichirou.
I see.
Then, Hyakuya,
we'll take you up on your offer and rest.
We'll leave lookout duty to you.
Sure! We won't let you down.
I guess friends really do die on missions.
Yes, they do.
That's what happens on the battlefield.
I know that too well.
Which is why we'll treasure every day and keep looking out for each other.
What are you guys just sitting around for?
You carried out your mission, right?
Isn't that obvious?
How about you?
Piece of cake.
Yeah, right.
Narumi.
Yes?
How did the newbies do?
Were they a nuisance?
Better than expected, I suppose...
To be honest,
I can't believe they're actually newbies.
Told you!
Don't get cocky!
Ow!
Aihara!
You lost eight men?
Yes.
I'm... I'm really sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
I was expecting casualties.
Your lost comrades have only me to blame.
No, this was my failure.
Hush.
You're still alive, that's good enough.
Narumi, what about the other squads?
Nothing yet.
I see.
Well, we can't afford to wait for them.
We're proceeding to the next objective.
The next objective?
Nine squads went to attack three nobles in city hall, and were annihilated.
Twenty-five of them were captured.
No...
To continue this battle, every single man counts.
That's why we're going to kill those nobles and rescue our comrades.
Lieutenant Colonel!
Let me come too!
I want to help you!
No.
I can't bring crybabies to the battlefield.
I'm kidding.
After we rescue our comrades,
we're going to regroup at the airport.
I need you to stay here and tell the other squads.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
All right, kiddos!
Sir!
Got a moment?
What?
Are you going to tell me not to do this because it's a trap?
No, we have to go, don't we?
After all, if we lose those squads, we won't have enough manpower to finish this battle.
Then what did you come to complain about?
Come on, I never said anything about complaining.
It's just that you're not one to take the death of your comrades lightly.
I just wanted see how you're holding up.
This is a battlefield.
A few sacrifices are to be expected.
Your willingness to bear the weight of those sacrifices is admirable.
It's okay.
They're the best. There's no way they'll lose.
You're right.
Let's believe in them and wait.
Squad Leader Aihara!
Guys! You're okay!
It wasn't easy, but we managed to kill our targets.
I'm so glad. Really, I'm so—
Run!
The Lieutenant Colonel's headed to the airport!
Regroup there!
Shit!
Human.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Everyone, initiate Code 284!
Huh? What the heck?
Seems like they killed themselves to avoid being tortured.
Poison hidden in your mouths, huh?
Sorry, I can't let you use that.
You need to answer my question, first.
Do your worst, I won't tell you—
Be quiet.
Play dead.
The others will realize you're still alive, if you don't.
Answer this, and I'll let you live.
Do you know anyone by the name Hyakuya Yuuichirou?
Your eyes tell me you do.
If you want to get out of this, tell me everything.
Kill me!
I'll never betray my comrades—
Shut up!
Yuu-chan isn't one of you!
Are you...
What are...
Hey, Mika, what are you up to over there?
This human's just like the others.
She killed herself.
But why would they do that?
Are they dumb?
Hey, you two.
What?
Look.
Vampires were killed here.
The one in charge of this area was Lucal Wesker-sama, right?
The humans couldn't possibly have killed a noble, could they?
Lacus-sama!
René-sama!
Our brethren underground have been completely annihilated!
What about Mel Stefano-sama?
We can't seem to find him.
Seriously?
This is getting pretty strange.
Indeed.
But for now, let's move.
Crowley-sama's supposed to be at the city hall.
Don't move!
One step and he's dead!
Were you spacing out or something, Mika?
That one's still alive.
Seize her, maybe we can extract some information.
I said don't move!
Don't you care if he dies?
Not really!
It's his fault if he dies.
Hold on.
I'll deal with this.
No talking!
Hyakuya Yuuichirou is...
heading to the city hall as we speak.
But if I let all of you go, they'll be killed for sure.
Why do you believe me?
I'm betting on the fact that you called our newbie "Yuu-chan."
Anyway, this is all I know.
You know what that means, right?
Die!
Nice.
Your other comrades took their own lives.
Yet here you are, trying to crawl away alive, like a coward.
Is your life so precious to you?
I-I don't want to die!
Don't kill me!
Then tell me where your other comrades are.
The ones who attacked this place, where are they now?
If I tell you... will you spare me?
Yeah.
Th-The Japanese Imperial Demon Army 2nd Company...
is currently on their way to the botanical garden in Higashiyama Park.
They intend to kill Zane Lindau!
Do you know him?
Do you not know him?
He's a 17th Progenitor.
So they even know the nobles' names and whereabouts.
This is getting bad.
What do we do?
We'll be in trouble if anyone finds out that we knew but didn't go to help.
We're going after them.
Aw, but it's so far away.
What a pain.
Wait.
Kill me.
I have nothing left.
Don't push your luck.
If you want to die, do it yourself.
I can't.
If I kill myself, they'll doubt my intel.
But if you kill me...
Hey, Mika! Hurry up, or we'll leave you behind.
Take the human with you, Mika.
We're not done with it?
Not yet.
We can still extract some—
Hey!
I'm tired of this!
You're just going to kill me in the end anyway, aren't you!?
Aw, you killed her.
We don't need intel from livestock.
Well, I guess that's true.
Still, these humans' fanatic loyalty is a bit scary.
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army seems like a disgusting organization.
Well, this is what always happens when humans gather together.
Anyway, we're heading for the botanical garden.
We can't let them kill the 17th Progenitor.
I'm taking a different route.
We can't just take a human's word at face value.
Give me five men.
We're going to check city hall, just in case.
Good point.
We'll leave that to you, then.
Did you...
protect Yuu-chan?
Of course not.
You were just using him.
Okay, let's get going.
We're going to investigate the city hall.
I'm coming, Yuu-chan.
What's wrong?
Nah, I just noticed the clouds coming in.
Perfect weather for a raid, don't you think?
Yeah, true.
reimei ni tsuki wa koroge ochite
The moon rolls away into the dawn
shitatakana kirameki ni kakusareru
hiding in the strong light
kanjou ni kanketsu suru omoi
Emotions circling back to closure
dare no kokoro mo tsunagenai
I can't connect anyone's hearts
yuuen no inori
A distant prayer
shinjiteita chitsujo ga uso naraba
If the peace that we believed in was a lie,
jibun no kokoro sura jyunshoku wo shite
I will even fool my heart
furuitateru honoo wo matou
and clothe myself in an inspiring flame
umidashite wa hakai suru hakoniwa
A garden creates, then destroys everything
tatoe nigiru tsurugi ga moroha demo
even if the sword you hold is double-edged
subete wo ushinau made aragai, torikustaa
Fight until you lose everything, trickster
Next time on Owari no Seraph:
Shinya and Guren
Shinya and Guren.